https://www.thedividendpig.com/privacy-policy/

Terms of ServiceThis statement of our Terms of Service, outlines our disclaimer and privacy policy. By use of this website you agree to these terms.DisclaimerThe Dividend Pig is not a professional financial advisor or investment dealer. This website does not offer professional or financial advice, and is intended to provide general information for educational and entertainment purposes only. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. The Dividend Pig is not responsible for the investment decisions you make. You should consult with a professional financial advisor before making any important investment decisions.This website also offers advertising by third parties. The Dividend Pig does not endorse or guarantee these services, and therefore we assume no responsibility for their accuracy or legitimacy.In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from third party advertising, content written, suggestions made on individual securities, loss of profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available via every page of our website, and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.Google AdSense Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses Double-Click DART cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google, enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website, as well as other sites on the Internet.To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL AdSense Network Privacy. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, The Dividend Pig has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.Google Analytics When visiting The Dividend Pig, the IP address used to access the site may be logged or masked along with the dates and times of access by Google Analytics. This information is not shared and purely used to analyze trends, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.You may visit the Google Analytics privacy policy at the following URL Analytics Privacy Policy.Collection of Personal InformationAt the Dividend Pig you have the option to post comments on this blog, subscribe to comments, or subscribe to a newsletter. Your personal information such as name, email address, website URL, and IP address, may be collected. This information is only used to facilitate commenting, and for us to correspond with you by email to receive our newsletters.Your personal information will never be shared or distributed with any other parties. You may also unsubscribe from the Dividend Pig at any time, at which point all personal information will be permanently removed.Links to third party WebsitesWe have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.Copyright and Use of this StatementThis Privacy Policy was generated by the AdSense Privacy Policy plugin.This Disclaimer is entirely written by The Dividend Pig, and is under all rights reserved and copyright protection. It is used on our website and other forms of media. This disclaimer is not to be distributed or used without prior permission.Changes to this StatementThe contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.If you have any questions regarding this Disclaimer or Privacy Policy then please contact us.TweetSharePinFlipRedditFollow Me
6.4K Facebook
Google Plus
Twitter
4.4K Pinterest
Recent Posts
Money in the Trough – December Dividend Stock Purchases – 2020 By Blake
Money in the Trough – November Dividend Stock Purchases – 2020 By Blake
October Dividend Income and Net Worth Report – 2020 By Blake
Money in the Trough – October Dividend Stock Purchases – 2020 By Blake
AboutDividend IncomeDividend Income & Net WorthDividend Growth StocksIf You Only Invested Then…A Little Motivation for NowA Short Story of Successful Dividend InvestingDividend PortfolioDividends 101Dividend Yield ChartsResourcesBlogRollGoalsSubscribe to The Dividend Pig Submit Type above and press Enter to search. Press Esc to cancel.
TweetSharePinFlipReddit
